https://www.stonestreet.com/privacy-policy/

Call 866-416-5118
Stone Street Capital Consumer Privacy Notice
This notice is effective as of January 1, 2020.
DATA COLLECTION AND USAGE POLICY
Stone Street Capital collects information via our website(s) using web forms.
The information collected by these web forms is used solely for the purpose of contacting the consumer for new applications, program qualifications and customer support and service. The web forms collect basic contact information such as name and email address and sometimes some basic financial qualification information for debt services that includes estimates of personal consumer debt.
The information and data collected from web forms is stored in an offline database that is not connected to or integrated with any other third party applications.
Furthermore, Stone Street Capital does not sell or share any data collected from our web forms with any third-party vendors for marketing or other purposes.
What does Stone Street Capital do with your personal information?
Stone Street Capital is part of The J.G. Wentworth Company® Family of Companies.
Why?
Companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the transaction(s) you have with us. This information can include:
• Social Security number and contact information (e.g.: name, address, telephone number(s), email)• Transaction information, details, and balances, transaction history and any other information resulting from a transaction with one of our divisions.• Credit history/credit score, information contained in public records, and any other information and documents you provide to us or authorize us to obtain.• Non-public health information, where applicable.
How?
Most companies need to share personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons we can share your personal information; the reasons we choose to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information:Do we reserve the right to share?Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes—such as to process and service your transactions, respond to court orders and legal investigations, report to credit bureaus, or as otherwise permitted by law.YesNo
For our marketing purposes—to offer our transactions to youYesNo
For joint marketing with other financial companiesYesNo
For our Affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your transactions and experiencesYesNo
For our Affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthinessYesYes
For our Affiliates to market to youYesYes
For Nonaffiliates to market to youYesYes
To Limit our sharing
Call 1-800-715-8127 or email us at privacy@jgwentworth.com
Please note: If we have no prior relationship with you, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we will continue to share your information as described in this notice.
However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing. Companies owned by The J.G. Wentworth Company may choose not to share nonpublic personal information with Affiliates or Nonaffiliates, even if that sharing is generally allowed.
Questions?
Call 1-800-715-8127 or email us at privacy@jgwentworth.com.When you call please spell your first and last name so we can correctly identify you. Also whether you call or email please state your reference number if listed on the letter you received. You may also contact us via mail at:
Customer Service – Privacy Coordinator – Legal Department
Stone Street Capital
1200 Morris Drive
Chesterbrook, PA 19087
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?
This notice is provided by Stone Street Capital and by The J.G. Wentworth Company on behalf of itself and certain of the various companies that it owns.
What we do
How do we protect your personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use administrative, physical, and technical security measures. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
Our control policies authorize access to customer information by individuals who need access to the information to do their work.
How do we collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you:
•	Request information or submit an application
•	Give us your contact information or otherwise provide information to us or authorize us to obtain it
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only:
• Sharing for Affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthiness.
• Affiliates from using your information to market to you
• Sharing for Nonaffilates to market to you
What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?
Your choices will apply to all transactions that you have completed where there was another customer also involved and will apply to their information as well.
Definitions
AffiliatesCompanies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. Our Affiliates include J.G. Wentworth, Peachtree, and others, please see our website for a full list www.jgwentworth.com/en/privacy-policy.
NonaffiliatesCompanies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
Joint marketingA formal agreement between nonaffiliated companies that together market transactions to you.
Other important information
Nevada:
We are providing you this notice pursuant to state law.
You may be placed on our internal Do Not Call List by following the directions in the section above entitled, “How can I limit the sharing of my information?”
Nevada law requires that we also provide you with the following contact information: Bureau of Consumer Protection, Office of the Nevada Attorney General, 555 E. Washington St., Suite 3900, Las Vegas, NV 89101; Phone number- 702.486.3132; email: BCPINFO@ag.state.nv.us.
The J.G. Wentworth Company, 1200 Morris Drive, Chesterbrook, Pennsylvania 19087; Phone Number:
1 (800) 715-8127 email: Privacy@jgwentworth.com.
Vermont:
In accordance with Vermont law, we will not share information we collect about Vermont residents with companies outside of our corporate family, except as permitted by law, such as with your consent, to service or audit or fund your transactions or with financial institutions (or other companies) with which we have joint marketing agreements.
We will not share information about your creditworthiness within our corporate family except with your authorization or consent, but we may share information about our transactions or experiences with you within our corporate family without your consent.
EFFECTIVE JANUARY 1, 2020
CALIFORNIA RESIDENT RIGHTS
As a California resident you have the following rights under the California Consumer Protection Act (CCPA):
You have the right to request that a business delete any personal information about you which the business has collected from you. The CCPA provides certain exceptions to the right to have personal information deleted.
You have the right to request, free of charge, that a business that collects personal information about you disclose to you the following information covering the 12 months preceding your request:
The categories of personal information it has collected about you;
The categories of sources from which the personal information is collected;
The business or commercial purpose for collection or selling personal information;
The categories of third parties with whom the business shares your personal information; and
The specific pieces of personal information it has collected about you.
You have the right to request, free of charge, that a business that sells personal information about you, or that discloses it for a business purpose, disclose to you the following information covering the 12 months preceding your request: :
The categories of personal information that the business collected about the Consumer.
The categories of personal information that the business sold about the you and the categories of third parties to whom the personal information was sold, by category or categories of personal information for each third party to whom the personal information was sold.
The categories of personal information that the business disclosed about the Consumer for a business purpose.
You shall have the right, at any time, to direct a business that sells personal information about you to third parties not to sell your personal information.
We do not sell any of your personal information.
A business shall not discriminate against you because you exercised any of your rights under the law.
To request information about your personal information, complete the form below:
First Name
Last Name
E-mail*
Submit Form
How we collect, use share personal information of Consumers
JG Wentworth has collected the following categories of personal information about Consumers in the twelve (12) months prior to the effective date of this policy:
Classification and method(s) of Information Collected
Demographic/Firmographics
Data Type
Name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, social security number, driver’s license number, passport number, or other similar identifiers.
Collection Method (s) – Website forms, call center operator, email
Business Purpose – Provide customers with buyouts of long-term financial settlements, lottery winnings and annuities as well as offer debt relief and settlement services for consumers.All information gathered is required to deliver said services.
Third Parties that we share this information with – JG Wentworth may share email address as a means of building “lookalike” audiences in both Facebook and Google for the purpose of advertising.
Online/Behavioral
Data Type – Internet or other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing history, search history, and information regarding a Consumer’s interaction with an Internet Web site, application, or advertisement.
Collection Methods – Website tracking software, First-party tracking cookies,web forms
Business Purpose – Advertising, communication, audience lookalike building improving web experience, customer service.
Third Parties that we share this information with – JG Wentworth may share email address as a means of building “lookalike” audiences in both Facebook and Google for the purpose of advertising.
Financial Information
Data Type – Name, signature, social security number, physical characteristics or description, address, telephone number, passport number, driver’s license or state identification card number, insurance policy number, education, employment, employment history, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information.
Collection Method (s)– Website forms, call center operator, email
Business Purpose – Provide customers with buyouts of long-term financial settlements, lottery winnings and annuities as well as offer debt relief and settlement services for consumers. All information gathered is required to deliver said services.
Third Parties that we share this information with – N/A
Commercial Data
Data Type – Data Type – Commercial information, including records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies.
Collection Method (s) – Website forms, call center operator, email
Business Purpose – Provide customers with buyouts of long-term financial settlements, lottery winnings and annuities as well as offer debt relief and settlement services for consumers. All information gathered is required to deliver said services.
Third Parties that we share this information with – N/a
HOW TO EXERCISE YOUR RIGHTS
To exercise the rights described above, you must submit a verifiable Consumer request to us by contacting us at 1 -800-715-8127 or email us at privacy@jgwentworth.com. We will acknowledge receipt of your request and advise you how long we expect it will take to respond if we are able to verify your identity. Requests for specific pieces of Personal Information may require additional information to verify your identity.
You may designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf. If you submit a request on behalf of another person as an authorized agent, we may require additional proof that you are authorized and information to verify the identity of the person for whom you are submitting a request.
In some instances, we may not be able to honor your request. For example, we will not honor your request if we cannot verify your identity or if we cannot verify that you have the authority to make a request on behalf of another individual. Additionally, we will not honor your request where an exception applies, or where the Personal Information that we maintain about you is not subject to the CCPA’s access or deletion rights.
We will advise you in our response if we are not able to honor your request. We will not provide social security numbers, driver’s license numbers or government issued identification numbers, financial account numbers, health care or medical identification numbers, account passwords or security questions and answers, or any specific pieces of information if the disclosure presents the possibility of unauthorized access that could result in identity theft or fraud or unreasonable risk to data or systems and network security.
We will work to process all verified requests within 45 days pursuant to the CCPA. If we need an extension for up to an additional 45 days in order to process your request, we will provide you with an explanation for the delay.
Website Privacy Notice
When you visit or browse our website, we and our advertising, marketing, or service partners may collect information such as your Internet Protocol or “IP” address, the “URL” of the web pages you visit, and may use “cookies,” web beacons, or other objects to collect statistical and other information about your use of the our website and other websites. The purpose of collecting this information is to improve the effectiveness of our website and to conduct targeted advertising or marketing. The collected information may include, for example, the web pages you visited; the date and time of your visit; the websites you visited immediately before and after visiting our web site; your language preference; demographic information; the kind of browser you use; and the popularity of various advertising words and phrases used by us. The collection of this information allows for the compilation of aggregate and anonymous information about the usage of our website and other websites.
Furthermore, our website also uses one or more media-players in order to deliver video content. Accordingly, the site may place a local shared object or “flash cookie” on your computer in order to enhance the functionality of such media-players and to remember personalized settings.
Your web browser should allow you to manage cookies and you can manage your Flash cookies by visiting http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html. “Flash” is a registered trademark of Adobe Systems Incorporated.
We define children as individuals under the age of 16. Our website is not intended for the use of children and we do not knowingly solicit or collect information from children.
THE J.G. WENTWORTH COMPANY FAMILY OF COMPANIES
The J.G. Wentworth Company family of companies includes:
